

THAI THI YEN NHI

Front-end Developer

nhithai88@gmail.com +84 974 833 783 nhidev.github.io

With a strong technical skill-set, attention to detail, and 4+ years of experience, I want to work as a front-end web developer where I could create digital magic and elevate user experience to the next level.

Experience

REDWEB

Front-end Developer

9/2017 - 6/2018 redweb.vn

- Creating, modifying websites for Joomla open source CMS and our ecommerce platform.
- Upgrade client sites (ecommerce platform, Joomla CMS).
- Fix front end related bugs that were identified in QA, beta and production environments.
- Attend wire frame review, design and html code walkthrough meetings.
- · Worked in Agile environment, attending daily scrum meetings.

1PAC

Front-end Developer

08/2016 - 06/2017 1pac.vn

- Develop HTML/CSS templates from Photoshop visual design and wireframes.
- Refactoring code and delivering products with high quality, write code that runs

 cross browsers.
- Research trending technologies and apply it to real production.

CANON LE BAO MINH

Web Developer

05/2014 - 07/2016 lebaominh.vn

- Creating, modifying websites for WordPress open source CMS solutions with PHP programming language.
- Used jquery to build accordion style content, drag and drop functionality, calendar, popup and modal windows
- Cross-browser compatible by writing W3C validated Semantic XHTML.
- Responsible for solving page layout issues and creating an effective CSS fluid layout.
- Monitored the web analysis reports to view the performance of the company websites.

SKUNKWORKS

Data Agent

06/2012 - 12/2013

Collect, verify data from multiple sources like Yelp, Foursquare, Opentable, Google+
 ... to build a social planning application "Klamr".

GHP FAR EAST (SWISS POST)

Data Agent

09/2010 - 08/2011

- Insert customer and account data by inputting text based and numerical information from source documents.
- Compile, verify accuracy and sort information according to priorities to prepare source data for computer entry.
- Review data for deficiencies or errors, correct any incompatibilities if possible and check output.

Skills

HTML/CSS	SASS/LESS	Javascript	Bootstrap		jQuery		Joomla
Wordpress	Photoshop	Webpack	Grunt	Github		Jira	

Education

Associate of Science from Hoa Sen University (2009) Bachelor of Science from Hutech University (2013)